sexyjobs.com 2018-08-11

# SexyJobs.com Basic User Terms of Service

We hereby publish this Our privacy policy concerning the personally identifiable information which We collect from You and the uses to which We will and will not put such information. _(What follows is the general Privacy Policy of this site; it makes reference to resumes and information contained in them. As provided for in this Agreement, Basic Users do not have the ability to post resumes here, though they may acquire the ability to do so by becoming a Job Seeker User. There is no charge associated with becoming a Silver Job Seeker User.)_

* ### 200.100.200.101 General

SexyJobs.com is committed to respecting the privacy of Our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to Our Website. By using SexyJobs.com, You consent to the policies and practices described in this Statement.

* ### 200.100.200.102 Children

Children under eighteen years of age are not eligible to use Our services. We ask that children do not submit information to Us.

* ### 200.100.200.103 Information We Collect

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part in the United States. If You access SexyJobs.com outside the United States, Your usage of that site constitutes consent to the transfer of Your data out of Your country and to the United States.

Our sites contain links to other web sites over which We have no control. SexyJobs.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other web sites to which You choose to link from a SexyJobs.com Website. We encourage You to review the privacy policies of those other web sites so You can understand how they collect, use and share Your information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to the information We collect on SexyJobs.com, and does not apply to information We collect in any other fashion.

* ### 200.100.200.104 Collection and Retention of Information

In some areas of Our Website, SexyJobs.com requests or may request that You provide personal information, including Your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, social security number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which Your identity is discernible. In other areas, SexyJobs.com collects or may collect demographic information that is not unique to You such as Your ZIP code, age, preferences, gender, interests and favorites. Sometimes We collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. Examples of areas on SexyJobs.com where We collect personal or combined personal and demographic data are pages where You can sign up to use a service, post a resume, post a help wanted ad, or purchase a product.

We also gather or may gather certain information about Your use of Our site, such as what areas You visit and what services You access. Moreover, there is information about Your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by SexyJobs.com. This information can include without limitation Your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses.

SexyJobs.com may sometimes afford You the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, behavioral, preferential and/or life style information about Yourself, but it is solely up to You whether You furnish such information. If You do provide such information, You are thereby consenting to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Statement. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining Your potential interest in receiving email or other communications about particular products or services.

Please remember that if You post any of Your personal information in public areas of SexyJobs.com, such as if You post Your resume to Our talent database, such information may be collected and used by others over whom SexyJobs.com has no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information You post or otherwise make available in public areas of SexyJobs.com.

We retain indefinitely all the information We gather about You in an effort to make Your repeat use with Us more efficient, practical, and relevant. Of course, You can correct or update Your SexyJobs.com account, resume or help wanted ad at any time. Moreover, You can delete Your resume or help wanted ad from Our online database or close Your account at any time, in which event We will remove all Our copies of Your resume, help wanted ad and SexyJobs.com account profile information except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet.

* ### 200.100.200.105 Use of Information by SexyJobs.com

We use the information We gather on SexyJobs.com, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the SexyJobs.com Website, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that We offer.

We may also use the information We gather to inform You of other products or services available from SexyJobs.com or its affiliated companies or to contact You about Your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. (The term "affiliated companies" is defined in the section of this Statement entitled "Contact Information.")

We may use Your contact information in order to send You e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the SexyJobs.com site, such as new SexyJobs.com opportunities and additional listings which may be of interest to You. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information We have about You. In addition, at the time of registration for SexyJobs.com, You have the option to elect to receive additional communications, messages, information and promotions including without limitation free informational newsletters from SexyJobs.com relating to topics that may be of special interest to You, such as career management advice.

We have an area where You can submit feedback. Any feedback You submit in this area becomes Our property, and We can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or contact You for further information.

* ### 200.100.200.106 Disclosure of Information to Others

We do not disclose to third parties Your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about Your use of SexyJobs.com (such as the areas You visit or the services You access), except as set forth in the following four subparagraphs.

We may disclose such information to third parties if You consent to such disclosure. For example, if You indicate that You would like to receive information about the products or services of third parties at the time You register for an account, We may supply Your contact information to third parties such as employers, recruiters, data aggregators, marketers or others for the purpose of sending You e-mail or otherwise communicating with You. We may use data We have about You (such as the interests and preferences You have expressed) to determine whether You might be interested in the products or services of a particular third-party.

We may disclose such information to companies and individuals We employ to perform functions on Our behalf. Examples may include hosting Our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to Your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party.

We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if We believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of SexyJobs.com or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.

We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of SexyJobs.com's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of Our assets. In addition, in the event SexyJobs.com becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, SexyJobs.com or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court.

SexyJobs.com may also share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to each of its web sites with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they may understand the kinds of visitors to SexyJobs.com's site and how those visitors use the site.

* ### 200.100.200.107 Resumes

Since SexyJobs.com is a career site, We give Job Seeker Users, as that term is defined above, the option of putting a resume in Our searchable database. When this is done, then all users with access to Our resume database (or copies thereof) will have access to the resume. We attempt to limit access to Our searchable database (or copies thereof) only to paying employers, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other users will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in Our searchable database. You may remove Your resume from Our searchable database at any time. However, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to that database or to obtain a copy of that database, as well as parties who have otherwise gained access to the database, may have retained a copy of Your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes in these instances.

* ### 200.100.200.108 Help Wanted Ads

Since SexyJobs.com is a career site, We give Help Wanted Users, as that term is defined above, the option of putting a help wanted and job or work opportunity want ad in Our searchable database. When this is done, then all users with access to Our help wanted database (or copies thereof) will have access to the ad. We attempt to limit access to Our searchable database (or copies thereof) only to sincere job seekers, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other users will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of ads by third parties who access such ads while they are in Our searchable database. You may remove Your ad from Our searchable database at any time. However, Job Seeker Users, Basic Users and others who have access to that database or who have obtained a copy of that database, as well as parties who have otherwise gained access to the database, may have retained a copy of Your ad in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of ads in these instances.

* ### 200.100.200.109 Use of Cookies

SexyJobs.com uses "cookies" to help personalize and maximize Your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on Your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to Your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to Your computer, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to You.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save You time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that You have returned to a specific page. For example, if You personalize SexyJobs.com pages, or register for services, a cookie helps Us to recall Your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of Our use of cookies, We can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When You return to the SexyJobs.com site, the information You previously provided can be retrieved, so You can easily use the features that You customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing.

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but You can usually modify Your browser setting to decline all cookies if You prefer. Alternatively, You may be able to modify Your browser setting to notify You each time a cookie is tendered and permit You to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If You choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact Your experience on the SexyJobs.com Website.

* ### 200.100.200.110 Updating Your Information

You may review, correct, update or change Your SexyJobs.com resume or help wanted ad at any time. You have the following choices to modify or delete Your information from our database:

[Send an email](https://www.sexyjobs.com/contact) to Our customer service department;

[Visit the job seekers area](https://www.sexyjobs.com/jobseekers/) to login with Your password and modify/delete Your resume;

[Visit the employers area](https://www.sexyjobs.com/employers/) to login with Your password and modify/delete Your help wanted ad;

Call Us by telephone at 855-799-5627 ext 2;

Send mail to the following postal address:

SexyJobs.com, InfoNet Publications Inc., 3470 E Russell Ste 280, Las Vegas, NV 89120.

* ### 200.100.200.111 Security

SexyJobs.com has implemented reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure Your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, We cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use Your personal information for improper purposes.

When You place an order online at SexyJobs.com, Your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for Your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. SexyJobs.com uses Plug and Pay Technologies, Inc. to process its credit card transactions.

* ### 200.100.200.112 Changes to Privacy Policy

If We decide to change Our Privacy Statement for SexyJobs.com, We will post those changes here so that You will always know what information We gather, how We might use that information, and to whom We will disclose it. If at any time, You have questions or concerns about SexyJobs.com's Privacy Statement, please feel free to [email Us](https://www.sexyjobs.com/contact).

* ### 200.100.200.113 Contact Information

SexyJobs.com is a name under which Infonet Publications, Inc., a Nevada corporation with its principal place of business at 3470 E Russell Ste 280, Las Vegas, NV 89120, and certain of its affiliated companies worldwide, do business. ("Affiliated companies" means entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with Infonet Publications, Inc.). Infonet Publications, Inc. is the legal entity which determines the purposes and means of processing the information gathered at SexyJobs.com. The information We gather on SexyJobs.com may be shared within Infonet Publications, Inc. and its affiliated companies, including its other web sites that are part of the SexyJobs.com Network. The SexyJobs.com Network consists of SexyJobs.com, AdultJobs.com, AdultIndustry.com, AdultIndustryJobs.com, AdultEmployment.com, AdultPerformers.com and PhoneActresses.com.

* ### 200.100.200.114 Comments

We welcome Your comments concerning this Privacy Statement. If You believe that We have not adhered to this Statement, please [contact Us](https://www.sexyjobs.com/contact) by email or by calling Us at 1-855-799-5627. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

Thank You for using SexyJobs.com!
